good morning this video is recorded on
Remembrance Day in Canada Veterans Day
in the United States and this is how we
achieve world peace
in our lifetime there are three
components to this one of which is
individually what we can do in groups
what we can do as well as globally and
as always the global is a tech
cooperative solution so individually we
can work on our own emotional
intelligence acknowledge when we're
feeling like we want to dominate or
punish an individual judge an individual
when we don't we have not walked a mile
in their shoes to come from the stance
of any individual we are dealing with is
doing the best job they can with their
current circumstance so if we want them
to do a better job we need to help them
change their current circumstance a big
way we can do that is in help is helping
people find and form groups because we
are social species and a lot of this is
easier when we're working in groups to
be able to deal with your own emotional
intelligence is one thing to be able to
have conversations in a group and help
ask for help in developing our emotional
intelligence ask for help in finding
where we're dominant and and then what
do we do about that do we do about those
emotions and to be able be able to find
groups is a piece of what a global tech
cooperative can give us and the tools to
be able to effectively use those groups
on the global side in order to be able
to tackle world peace we need to be
simultaneously creating solutions to
poverty to climate change and to all of
the things that can lead to more chaos
and war on our planet but one of the
things we can do with technology and
probably honestly has already been done
just need to find those apps final at
Beth's websites and make them widely
available and bring them together is to
track or track every bombing every drone
strike every act of terrorism
where did it happen how many people died
how do we know what happened there and
then from the thing that is black and
white or more black and white we can
then look at the gray area who was
responsible if we don't know who did the
drone strike do we know who made the
drone because that's what we need to
tackle we need to the people that are
making money off of human beings
murdering each other in a systematic way
you need to be held accountable and they
are made up of individuals who are doing
the best job they know how to do under
their current situation they are playing
a game of profit and it's costing us our
lives so we need to help them do better
which means if they're not going to work
on their emotional intelligence we need
to hit them where they care which is in
their wallets so we need to track every
dollar we need to track I don't buy
drones I don't buy bass weapons of mass
destruction and so I can't choose to
spend that money more wisely somewhere
else but we can track every person that
is a board member every person that is a
CFO CEO everyone who's a top shareholder
we can see where else they spend their
money and we can choose to boycott them
once we boycott those companies once we
say and part a big piece of this isn't
something we could create tomorrow
because we need to have alternatives if
I'm spending my money in a company
because it's giving me value it's giving
me something that I can afford it's
convenient it's the only place it's a
monopoly in my life it's not as easy to
switch to something else so when we
offer people actual real alternatives to
the ones that are corrupt when we can
show that they are corrupt then we give
people an alternative just voting with
their money
in a way that promotes war and
environmental degradation and poverty so
that's why we're also need to tackle all
of those things at once when people are
fed clothed sheltered have their
education and their healthcare needs met
they have much more power to then
start voting with their dollar to choose
where they are choosing to be employed
because when your needs are met and your
it's not about starvation why would you
go and work for someone who's who's
directly responsible for murder and
fellow human beings and it's not an
alignment with your values and so by
creating some tools that help us track
the money that helped us organize and
utilize the information that's already
out there these companies are publicly
traded we already know who the CFO and
CEOs are we already know who the board
members are following them so that every
other company doesn't want to be
associated with them anymore
they're gonna pull themselves off of the
board they're gonna quit their job as a
CFO and CEO when it means that their
portfolio is hurt hurt them where they
care so as individuals working our
emotional intelligence being able to
find groups that we align with so that
as we evolve we don't feel like we're
gonna be leaving behind our entire
community as a globe looking and
tracking the information that we are
directly responsible for if we're
spending money that's going towards
making somebody richer who's causing
human misery that's our responsibility
and we can organize that information and
we can create world peace in our
lifetime with these tools we care we
don't want to hurt one another been
shown time and time again that soldiers
on the battlefield and I'm firing over
each other's heads and and or if when
they're forced to kill each other come
back with mental and emotional issues we
want to do good we want to help one
another and when we don't when we can
own that individually when we can own
those pieces of it that happens
throughout the day I'm like okay no I
don't want to have person to have good I
need to look at me and figure it out and
so when we're able to do we don't do it
all at once what about the little pieces
of that and help each other to pieces of
that we can create world peace in our
lifetime this is the first time we've
had more visible on the scale it's
visible delivered to us in HD on our
screens and it's the first time we have
the technology and tools to be able to
combat it at a global level just
no more no more are you going to fight
war with my money and my vote no more in
that world world peace doesn't just
become possible it becomes probable we
can take back our power as people and
create a world that works for everyone
thank you